Every time the rain no longer
falls, and I see the sky,
I think back to when I was a child.
Who could only cry.
Blindly chasing after him.
I fell far behind my only thought.
One day I will be stronger.
Grattery and gratitude.
Fading with the wind.
Am I stronger now than I was before?
Or as weak as back then?
I don't know for sure.
But until I do, my voyage will not end.
No matter what's next, I'm
walking straight ahead.
So let's go, there's nothing
that can stop us now.
Though time roll on our side,
we'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall, but we'll
always keep on standing.
There's no way anything
will take what I hope.
The voices inside me push
me to keep surviving.
I'll go on, I'll get through,
no matter what I gotta do.
The fiercest thoughts
of all can pour upon me.
I don't care why in the
world would I turn back.
So let's go.
There's nothing that can stop us now.
Though time's not on our side.
We'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall.
But we'll always keep on standing.
There's no way anything will take.
What I hope dear away from me.
I know the future's there for us to see.
I don't have time to get in a
fight with such a strong guy!
All I'm here to do is save Aix!
Go!
Second gear!
Don't worry, we'll deal with fancy pants!
Yee-haw-ha! Yeah!
Hey, Hawkeye!
Remember the time we challenged you?
Well, here comes a blast of
the past to kick your smug ass!
We're powered up now as new
commas, and you're gonna feel it!
Woo-hoo!
I don't remember you.
You're worms.
In a long line of them.
Almost there!
Keep running and don't look back!
You're still, in rage.
Ow! Man!
He got me!
He's going in for the kill!
Bastard!
Gum-gum-gum!
Jet-bun-gum!
Too close.
He'd have sliced my arms
right off if I'd attacked.
So, you're smarter than you look.
Okay, a sword should not do that.
Could we please call that thing
something other than a sword?
He's definitely earned that
world's strongest swordsman title.
He's stronger than a mountain of ice.
There's no way Strawhead's gonna
survive, not if he's fighting here!
That's why you don't slice Icebergs!
Stop looking at me like you're my
equal because you're far from it.
If anything, you should
be begging to work for me.
Well then,
and here I thought you'd
been humbled by prison
but not even impelled down
could make a dent in you.
Damn straight.
I've heard enough talk.
Sable!
Get lost, you Gecko!
I assumed you could be reasoned
with, but I was obviously mistaken.
These dumb jawheads don't notice
you if you don't try to fight them.
We can just breathe through.
That's not a breeze!
Get in, Dock!
Whoa!
He literally got sucked in
from someone else's neck!
Stop! Now!
You'll never make it to
your brother in time!
You shall perish after all.
Just freezing through,
nothing strange here.
There's no denying his
fighting skills have improved.
But I've already seen all his moves.
There's no chance that I'll miss again.
Not from such a close distance.
Don't find me, just passing through.
Nice save.
Jet human shield.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
I'll die!
What?
I didn't slice you.
Besides, I just heard
you say, don't mind me.
I'm here to save you.
There is no way your hearing
is that selfishly selective.
Gum-Gum!
Human shield!
Cut it out!
All right!
Enough!
Your sword's not working.
Suffer the special
muggy ball and blow off!
Or maybe not.
You want to hear a joke instead?
How's the muggy ball like
a robust financial market?
I don't know.
How is it?
Say it together, everyone.
Because it goes... BOOM!
I've never heard that one before.
Nice, Captain Buggy.
Good one.
Thank you, Buggy!
See you in the afterlife, I guess!
We're not done.
Vista pop said to make
sure ace's brother doesn't
get killed now go back him
up certainly I shall make a
We meet at last your reputation
precedes you flower sword vista
It's a pleasure to meet you, too.
I'm thrilled you've heard of me.
You can drop the false modesty.
Well, that sucked.
That mustache guy, who is he?
I see Straw Hat's true strength.
Well, thanks, whoever you are!
It's nothing to do with physical strength.
His power is to rally those around him.
That's the spirit, straw boy!
Keep running.
Luffy, save your brother.
You can do it!
Out of my way!
Of all the people seeking
to conquer the sea,
he may possess the greatest talent of all.
Ace!
In the looming shadow of
Ace's impending execution,
the world has been rocked by
one revelation after another.
It all began when more
than 200 inmates managed
to escape from the iron-tight
prison of Impel Dawn,
and the most notorious of those prisoners
have now taken a lead
role in this epic battle.
The blood-soaked expanse of the ghastly
battlefield is an unearthly sight,
and with a single glance at its horrors,
it's clear that this
showdown will change history.
The populace of the world has no choice
but to helplessly observe the events of
this war with the knowledge that its
outcome will determine their very future.
Fleet Admiral, everything
has been arranged.
The bay is fully prepared
as well. Yes, sir.
We're all set.
What they're already
preparing for the execution
those bastards they're
pushing up the schedule?
Are they damn we don't have much time!
Hold on is it really
about to happen that's
ridiculous why would
they announce the time?
And then change it at the
last minute have to feed
kill every single video
broadcast out of this place!
As representatives of
the navy and the world
government we're fighting
to preserve the Righteous
cause of absolute justice
and we must prevail
even if that means stepping over the line!
But it's too much for this naive world
to understand let alone see there's
no reason To submit innocent citizens
to the horrific imagery about to unfold?
Pops.
Run faster!
Damn it, looks like they really are
going to execute Ace ahead of time.
Ace!
The only news that should spread
throughout the world after this war
is on our victory.
And the details are irrelevant.
They're attacking our ships.
Look at the Bayhead,
there's something out there!
Pretty sure they're not on our side.
The Navy must have found a way to get some
reinforcements around
the ice wall somehow?
But are they admirals?
I mean, these guys are blowing up ships.
Shouldn't they be up front?
Is that...?
What?
What the hell are they?
Of course, I wondered when I'd get a
glimpse of the government's human weapons.
It's that big bear guy or i guess
i mean guys there's so many.
I'm confused a mere hour
and a half has passed
since the war began but
the navy aims to end it.
In one strike with this critical
push the tide of the war
has once again changed course
flowing into its final stage.
I'm tired of waiting
let's get this done!
They all look just like the warlord.
Kuma no way.
It's gotta be some kind of an illusion.
Well this just got weird.
I think I know those guys.
They went on a rampage here a while back.
It's like having an army of warlords.
But there weren't that
many when they attacked us.
Head office!
Reporting in!
You gotta hear this!
Hello? Anyone?
So this one's gotta be the
real kuma right I thought
this was just some rumor
but I've heard Word that Dr.
Vegapunk has been working on some
kind of human weapon and he's been
shipping out The prototypes to back
up the navy this could be them well
that looks like a human weapon if
I've Ever seen one sure but why are
they all kuma hey uncle this isn't
looking like the plan we talked about!
I thought the pirates were supposed
to be rounded up inside the bay
so we could pick them off
like fish in a barrel.
Why are they scattered all over the place?
I believe I've deciphered the Navy's plan.
They leaked the intel about the
decision to expedite Ace's execution,
knowing that it would send
us into a frenzy to save him.
After that,
all they had to do was slowly back up their
Forces to fully lure us pirates into the
bay and then they block off the bay head
with their human weapons to close the trap
checkmate now it all
makes sense that's why
White Beard ordered us
to sink those navy ships
instead of advancing he saw through their
plan if it weren't for
him we would have been
trapped yeah we can still attack from the
front and the rear even
if they're not closed
in the bay stick to the plan and take down
the Allied forces first
eliminate any parent
that's trying to stray from the enclosure
to advance and there
you go got it and if our
ships get caught in
the crossfire let's try
to keep it to a minimum
okay so that's the plan
Then time to work light up
as many kumas as you want
Now fire!
That's a feast dance!
They vaporized them!
Shit!
Bastards are even willing
to sacrifice their own men.
Don't lose faith!
March on!
Charge the plaza with all of your might!
The only retreat I know is death.
But I'll rescue Ace!
Before they can send me down that road?
All units get off the ice.
And defend the front line now!
Do whatever it takes.
To ensure the pirates don't
reach the plaza? Go! Fall back!
Hurry!
It's quite the unexpected
pleasure to cross
blades with the world's
greatest swordsman.
Your swordsmanship is of
no small renown either.
We were certain to cross paths.
Now show me your skill.
I'm happy to give you a peek!
What flowers would you like on your grave?
Onward!
Drive them in! Hell no!
La sequinence!
How's that feel?
There's no way those things
are made of flesh and bone.
Well, they're obviously not human.
Then what are they?
What happened to the screen?
Hey, what happened to the screen?
Struggle all you want, White Beard.
We still have the upper hand.
Ready to crush you!
As soon as every video feed has been cut,
activate the encircling walls and once
that's set, we will Immediately execute Ace.
and round up all of our remaining enemies.
Yes, sir!
Move it!
They're about to kill
Ace! I'd better hurry!
Sorry, back to square one.
Luffy, no!
Team Bay!
The Admiral's getting in on the fight!
Damn it!
Yet we must press on regardless.
We knew we would face insurmountable
odds and undefeatable foes.
Them sending out their best only means
we're too close for their comfort.
Time to die, son of dragon.
Hey, Ace's brother, you're not
running out of steam, are you?
White Beard's commanders, we won't
find any better backup than that.
You can't let one man halt
your advance now follow us
Yeah, let's take them
the name is pulling back.
So now's our chance.
We're breaking through these bastards
Lock here.
It's a real fight
Well if it isn't 10th
Division Commander Carol
look at that angry glower
do you really want to die?
With such a sour face you do realize you'll
be buried in this bay if you stay here
first taste Will die and then your cronies
will be trapped and wiped out i honestly
couldn't care less about Who's gonna win
this war but watching
White Beard die that's
fun pops and ace won't
die not while I'm around
shall
we put
this match on hold?
Vista
Much as I hate to we do have
other matters to worry about
We've got to back down So let's go
Smoker Didn't you hear the orders?
Yeah.
I heard them.
Next time, Straw Hat.
Luffy, you can do it. Stay strong.
Where the hell hasn't
the video feed been cut?
Sorry, sir.
It'll just be another minute.
We're all set.
Hey, Gaffer, you're blocking the shot.
It seems like they've cut all
the camera feeds except for one.
What's going on down there?
What is this feed?
Wait, is that who I think it is?
Oh, it is!
I can't believe it's him!
He's been laying low for
all these years, but...
He was a member of the legendary
crew that served under Gold Roger,
the king of the pirates!
Huh?
Who is it?
Can it really be the renowned
pirate Captain Buggy? Huh?
I'm sorry, did someone say my name? Huh?
It is classified
information, but I admit it.
I am the legendary pirate.
Hey, hold it, Captain Page. Stop.
You've got a nose blade.
Come out, sir, man.
Thank you, dammit.
What the hell is happening here?
How many times have I ordered you
fools to cap the stupid video?
We can't move with the world watching.
I understand,
sir,
but I'm afraid that the
escaped prisoners have somehow
managed to steal one of the
video transponder snails from us.
What?
How did you let this happen?
Makeup.
Ready to roll.
All right, guys, mark it.
Take two in three, two, one, and...
Oh, is that who I think it is?
The legendary crew member
of Gold Roger and the
sworn brother of Shanks
of the Four Emperors?
Could it really be the
mythical pirate, Captain Buggy?
Did someone say my name?
Stop those idiots right this second!
Oh, that was close!
They found us one for it!
I just saw you get sliced in half
by the infamous Hawkeye Mihawk,
but there's not even a scratch on you!
Oh, me?
That's right, I'm Buggy!
The living legend! Throw them away!
I want them dead!
Cut back to the war, dammit!
Why are we getting video of this moron?
Go back to Ace!
We're gonna miss the execution!
I wanna see that army
of Bartholomew Kumars!
Stand tall, men!
We can't stop now!
Not until we know that
Ace is safe! Let's go!
Hey, Pops.
Oh, Squad.
Good to see you're alive.
Yeah, barely.
Is that so?
I was trying to reach you earlier.
How are things looking
at the bay head now?
I'm sorry to say, but your
allies were beaten pretty badly.
Little does he know it works in our favor
for them to attack us from the rear.
I'm joining the fight.
Our only chance is to
keep pushing forward.
I couldn't agree more.
What's Squared doing up there?
You have 43 allied captains
willing to die for you.
We're all in your debt,
for now and for always.
We consider it a privilege to risk
our lives for you and your crew.
I don't know.